<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on paul-ylz</title>
    <link>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on paul-ylz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 13:58:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>React Native Localized Server Errors</title>
      <link>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/react-native-localized-server-errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 13:58:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/react-native-localized-server-errors/</guid>
      <description>An example of localizing server error responses and displaying them using React Native&amp;rsquo;s &lt;code&gt;Alert.alert&lt;/code&gt;. This implementation assumes Redux-Form</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squash &amp; Merge</title>
      <link>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/software-dev/squash-rebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 22:29:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/software-dev/squash-rebase/</guid>
      <description>At work we do TBD (Trunk Based Development), which means that we always push code to the master branch. Sometimes, pushing to master is not convenient because we are in the middle of figuring out a solution and some wild trial and error is the only way we can figure out how to move forward. We often want others in our team to be able to join forces with us and help to figure out the problem, and so the most convenient thing to do is to push the existing state of our code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copying and Pasting in Arch linux with Suckless Simple Terminal</title>
      <link>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/arch-linux/suckless-copy-paste/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 17:32:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/arch-linux/suckless-copy-paste/</guid>
      <description>Patch Simple Terminal so that there is just a single clipboard. https://st.suckless.org/patches/clipboard/
If like me, you had never patched a C file before&amp;hellip;
cd src/st-0.8.1 wget https://st.suckless.org/patches/clipboard/st-clipboard-0.8.1.diff patch &amp;lt; st-clipboard-0.8.1.diff Amazing!
If like me, maybe you also weren&amp;rsquo;t aware that copy and paste inside ST uses the keys: Control-Shift C (copy) and Control-Shift V (paste)
Install Chris Down&amp;rsquo;s clipmenu (AUR) clipnotify (AUR) is a dependency of clipmenu. With AUR, dependencies that are also AUR / community sourced have to be installed manually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bluetooth</title>
      <link>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/arch-linux/bluetooth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 17:49:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/arch-linux/bluetooth/</guid>
      <description>sudo pacman -S bluez blues-utils Check stuff is unblocked with rfkill list</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethernet</title>
      <link>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/arch-linux/ethernet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 17:49:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/arch-linux/ethernet/</guid>
      <description>Ethernet does not necessarily work out of the box - in which case the lights on the ethernet port will not even blink. To enable: See ethernet devices
$ ip link Then enable the ethernet device
$ ip link set dev &amp;lt;devicename&amp;gt; up  is the one that looks something like &amp;ldquo;enp0s31f6&amp;rdquo;
Then get DHCP working for that interface. I am able to just run
% sudo dhcpcd </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fonts in Arch</title>
      <link>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/arch-linux/font/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 17:49:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/arch-linux/font/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s pretty easy to set font in the Virtual Console. pacman -S terminus-font setfont ter-v32n
Voila, eyes saved.
I found it a bit trickier setting the font within X / dwm / st.
On the T460S I used X with dwm as the window manager, and st (simple terminal) to get the all important tty. Initially, the fonts inside my ttys were screwy - as in microscopic and also the kerning was totally wack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Dropbox w Cryptomator</title>
      <link>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/arch-linux/dropbox-with-cryptomator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 17:49:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paul-ylz.github.io/posts/arch-linux/dropbox-with-cryptomator/</guid>
      <description>https://wiki.archlinux.org/index.php/Dropbox
pacman -S dropbox I just run Dropbox when I&amp;rsquo;m in Xorg, so using ~/.xinitrc:
/usr/bin/dropbox &amp;amp; The next time you start X, Dropbox will pop open a browser to sign in with. After you sign in, ~/Dropbox will just automatically sync.
Cryptomator lets you store encrypted vaults on Dropbox. Unlocked vaults are made available via webdav, so some type of webdav client is needed. I tried nautilus and it worked, so I am using that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>